<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sam Cook</title>
    <link>https://www.samcook.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sam Cook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 18:26:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.samcook.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use fewer Google Services (and why you might want to).</title>
      <link>https://www.samcook.dev/blog/google/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 18:26:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.samcook.dev/blog/google/</guid>
      <description>Google is big, so what? Google and the services/products that they offer have become nearly ubiquitous pieces of modern life. Between emails and video calls, navigation, Android phones, internet searching, and watching videos, one can spend nearly their entire time online using a Google service on Google hardware.
As someone who used to use all of these services, the accuracy of recommmendations can be startling&amp;ndash;from suggested music, videos, and searches to potential restaurants, email compositions, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.samcook.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 20:33:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.samcook.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Sam. I&amp;rsquo;m a software developer and data enthusiast currently living in Heidelberg, Germany.
In 2018 I graduated from the Honors Program at Temple University where I studied math and computer science. They even let me speak at graduation!
I&amp;rsquo;m interested in many topics around big data, including distributed systems, data streaming, cloud native computing, machine learning, computer vision, and data science.
In my free time, aside from programming, my interests include biking, film photography, rock climbing, travelling, reading, and seeking the perfect cup of coffee.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>